Some things are better left unsaid.
Dirty Weekend is a drama, comedy film directed by Neil LaBute.
During a layover in Albuquerque, work colleagues Les and Natalie discover
more about each other than they ever thought possible.
Anxious and irritable, Les is drawn back into the city by past experiences he can’t forget (even
if he doesn't really remember the particulars of his previous drunken adventure).
Natalie, refusing to leave his side, follows along as her own secrets are
slowly revealed, leaving her feeling both vulnerable and unbound.
Les Moore, played by Matthew Broderick.
Natalie Hamilton, played by Alice Eve.
Cabbie, played by Phil Burke.
Dylan, played by Gia Crovatin.
Dark Haired Beauty, played by Monique Candelaria.
Vince, played by Charles Duran.
Dirty Weekend is a 2015 comedy drama film written and directed by Neil LaBute
and starring Matthew Broderick, Alice Eve, and Phil Burke.
Produced by Duncan Montgomery, Tiller Russell, and Joey Stewart, with
Executive Producers Cody Davis, Jack Selby & James Jackson Leach.
Shot in Albuquerque, New Mexico.
The film explores themes of hotel, infidelity,
airport, male homosexuality, relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.